SUPRIYA SINGH

Writer/Editor

+91 7231888260

♀ Indore, MP

@ singhsupriya24886@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/supriyasingh-286971219/

SUMMARY

I am a dedicated writer with over two years of prolific experience writing articles for college magazines, clubs, and websites. Skilled in writing topnotch articles and converting copy for landing pages. Ability to work with minimal supervision, with excellent interpersonal skills.

EXPERIENCE

Website Writer and Editor

Feedbox

= 09/2021 - 01/2022 Indore, MP

Feedbox is a Digital Marketing Agency that helps Businesses & funded Startups achieve business metrics like Revenue, Growth, and Customer Acquisition.

- Produced engaging and technically sound content as a Content Writer for Feedbox, producing specialized 28+ technical blogs for Quaff Media based in Delhi.
- Used advanced writing techniques to convey complex concepts clearly for technical and non-technical audiences.
- Demonstrated adaptability by swiftly grasping new topics and delivering high-quality content within tight deadlines.

Content Writer & Marketing Strategist Intern

TEdxPandri, FeedBox

m 12/2021 - 01/2022 O Indore, MP

Feedbox is a Digital Marketing Agency that helps Businesses & funded Startups achieve their business metrics like Revenue, Growth and Customer Acquisition.

- Served as an volunteer trainee in both the Marketing and Content Writing teams of Feedbox, contributing to TedxPandri as their official marketing partner.
- Collaborated with the Marketing team to devise and execute strategic marketing campaigns, focusing on maximizing audience engagement and event reach.

Content Writer and Volunteer

= 2021 - 2023 Indore, MP

The National Service Scheme is an Indian government sector public service program conducted by the Ministry of Youth Affairs and Sports of the Government of India.

- Volunteering for activities.
- Writing reports for the activities conducted.
- Acted as an anchor in the college activities and worked as a magazine editor and writer for 'AAROHNAM'.

SKILLS

Creative writing

MS Word

Google Analytics

Google Docs

SEO editing and keywords

Grammarly

Professional Writing

Blog Writing

Plagiarism Check

Marketing and Management

Web designing

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology (Civil Engineering- 8.65 CGPA)

Institute of Engineering & Technology DAVV

苗 2020 - Present

12th CBSE Board (89%)

Shiv Jyoti Convent School

10th CBSE Board (93%)

St. Joseph's Convent Sr. Sec School

STRENGTHS



Punctual

Complete tasks in tight schedule and timelines.



Communication

Using relevant knowledge, know-how, and skills to explain and clarify thoughts and ideas.

> Powered by CX7 Enhancy